Frosty Returns is a animation, family, tv movie film directed by Bill Melendez.
Twitchell, a greedy old businessman, has invented Summer Wheeze:
a spray that instantly removes snow and slush!
Now Holly has to keep Frosty from melting, and convince
everybody that snow's actually a good thing.
Narrator (Voice), played by Jonathan Winters.
Frosty the Snowman (voice), played by John Goodman.
Holly (voice), played by Elisabeth Moss.
Mr. Twitchell (voice), played by Brian Doyle-Murray.
Lil (voice), played by Jan Hooks.
Miss Carbuncle (voice), played by Andrea Martin.
Frosty Returns is an American animated Christmas television special directed by Bill Melendez and Evert Brown, starring the
voices of Jonathan Winters as the narrator, John Goodman as Frosty the Snowman, and Brian Doyle Murray as Mr.
It is the fourth special in a series beginning with Rankin/Bass Animated
Entertainment's 1969 television adaptation of Steve Nelson and Walter E.
"Jack" Rollins's 1950 holiday song.
It was produced by Bill Melendez Productions in association with
Broadway Video and CBS Entertainment Productions in 1992.
It premiered on CBS on December 1, 1992, and released on VHS by Family Home Entertainment
as part of their "Christmas Classics Series" line on September 15, 1993.
The film explores themes of holiday, musical, family
relationships, snowman, christmas.